When I tell you that God got me and my ancestors got me.
Jewish business leaders transformed the media landscape with an $8 billion deal.
Quote, in a groundbreaking strategic move reshaping the U.S. media market,
Brandon Korff, heir to the Paramount Empire,
has decided to sell control of the media and film empire to David Ellison,
heir to Larry Ellison's media empire.
So you have two pro-Israel heirs to billionaire fortunes
doing a little game with each other,
selling Paramount from one to the other.
The deal valued at $8 billion stands out as one of the most significant
and intriguing transactions in the U.S. media market,
showcasing the next generation of the world's most influential Jewish business leaders.
These two young men love Israel, are connected to their Judaism,
have Zionist values, and it's very encouraging to see
that in such successful families, the values are passed on to the younger generations.
Both quietly donate quite a bit to the state of Israel and the IDF.
And then, bizarrely, the article ends with this phrase.
This article was written in cooperation with Skydance.
Skydance is the corporate entity that was formed by the Ellisons to buy Paramount.
So I don't know what this arrangement was exactly,
but according to the Jerusalem Post,
the article that they reported on these two Jewish billionaires
in their plan to transfer the control of Paramount and CBS News from one to the other
with all of their pro-IDF and pro-Israel values
was an article written in cooperation with the company itself,
almost like an ad or a press release.
So, in other words, there's really no way to even continue participating in Hollywood
unless you are participating in the advancement of Zionist ideals.
Because I was pushed out.
However, I feel like I was also pulled out
because I would never have been able to sustain once I know what I know about Zionists.
And that it is one thing to be Jewish, it is another thing to be Zionist.
And that Jewish people really don't have any problem
with you calling out when there is a consolidation of power
unless they are ultimately going along with the narrative
that to call that out is to somehow put them in harm's way.
When the truth is, whenever there's a consolidation of power,
it should always be called out
and challenged on how it is using that power.
And we know that Zionists continue to push Jewish supremacy and apartheid.
They continue to push the occupation of Palestine, Lebanon, Syria,
and the occupation of the United States.
What do you think they're doing in our government?
So, in case there's any confusion, what I'm saying is all of my former peers,
y'all are now working for...
Fill in the blanks in the comments.
Who are they now working for?
You're damn rude, eh?